Guide to the Lifwynn Foundation Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Additional material, Accession 1999-M-082
  - Memos on Research (Box 15)
  - Research Publications, 1978-1981 (Box 15)
  - Research Publications Project, 1977 (Box 15)
  - Research Station-Subsidiary-Lifwynn Camp (Box 15)
  - Resident Agent in Maryland (Box 15)
  - Resource, Repository & Preservation, 1974-1981 (Box 15)
  - Rex Bookbindery (Box 15)
  - Herta Riese (Box 15)
  - Dr. Walther Riese, 1951-1981 (Box 15)
  - Professor David Riesman (Box 15)
  - Dr. Deborah Rinzler (Box 15)
  - Dr. Margaret J. Rioch (Box 16)
  - Riverside Community (Box 16)
  - Dr. Paul Roazen (Box 16)
  - Professor A. A. Roback (Box 16)
  - Mflry Alice Roche (Box 16)
  - Mary Alice Roche-Sensory Awareness (Box 16)
  - Margaret S. Weatherly Rockoff (Box 16)
  - Laurance Rockefeller (Box 16)
  - Dr. Henry Roger (Box 16)
  - Dr. Steve Rosen (Box 16)
  - Dr. Max Rosenbaum (Box 16)
  - Dr. Saul Rosenzweig (Box 16)
  - Ms. Louise Ross (Box 16)
  - Routledge & Kegan Paul Ltd., 1952-1977 (Box 16)
  - Royalties From All Publications (Box 16)
  - Dr. & Mrs. Theodore Roszak (Box 16)
  - Dr. Janis Roze (Box 16)
  - Richard A. Rutherford (Box 16)
  - R-Rz (Box 16)
  - Dr. Eugene Sachs (Box 16)
  - Thomas Sancton (Box 16)
  - Dr. C. R. Sankaran (Box 16)
  - Martena T. Sasnett (Box 16)
  - Anne Wilson Schaef (Box 16)
  - Dr. Leo Schelbert (Box 16)
  - Science and Man's Behavior (Box 16)
  - Dr. W. Clifford Scott (Box 16)
  - Sein Tu (Box 16)
  - Sensory Awareness (Box 16)
  - SALG Meeting Material (Box 16)
  - Selver/Brooks (Box 16)
  - SAF- (Charlotte Selver Foundation), 1982-1990 (Box 16)
  - Dr. Edwin C. Severinghaus (Box 16)
  - Dr. David Shainberg, 1976-1992 (Box 16)
  - Dr. Kunio Shiomi (Box 17)
  - Mrs. Alfreda Sill, 1938-1982 (Box 17)
  - A. P. Sill-Renewal of Our Common Neurosis, 1980 (Box 17)
  - Mr. & Mrs. Gerald Smaldone (Box 17)
  - Dr. David Smillie (Box 17)
  - Alice Smith (Box 17)
  - Mrs. Graham Smithwick (Box 17)
  - Social Consciousness & Human Survival (Box 17)
  - Dr. Anders Sola (Box 17)
  - Dr. Marvin Solit (Box 17)
  - Somatics-"Trigant Burrow and the Phylobiological Perspective" (Box 17)
  - Pitirim A. Sorokin (Box 17)
  - Spartan Press, 1971-1986 (Box 17)
  - Mrs. Carola H. Speads (Box 17)
  - Dr. Larry Spence (Box 17)
  - Spence Paper (Box 17)
  - Spencer Proposal (Box 17)
  - Dr. Michael Sperber, 1952-1991 (Box 17)
  - Professor A. Spina-Franca (Box 17)
  - Allen J. Sprow (Box 17)
  - Dr. Balthasar Staehelin (Box 17)
  - Frederick Stahly, 1972-1991 (Box 17)
  - Dr. Adolph Stem (Box 17)
  - Mrs. James Storrow (Box 17)
  - Dr. Herbert S. Strass (Box 17)
  - Mrs. Virginia Stuart (Box 17)
  - Dr. Gunnar Svenzon (Box 17)
  - John S. Swift Co. (Box 17)
  - Swiss American Historical Society (Box 17)
  - Anthony Syz (Box 17)
  - Dr. & Mrs. Hans Syz, 1951-1989 (Box 17)
  - Dr. Hans Syz (Box 17)
  - Dr. Hans Syz-Smithsonian Institution (Box 17)
  - Syz Publication (Box 17)
  - Syz Manuscript, 1995 December 12 (Box 17)
  - John Syz (Box 17)
  - Stephan Syz (Box 17)
  - S- Sz (Box 17)
  - Dr. Yasuhiko Taketomo (Box 17)
  - Dr. Charles Tart (Box 17)
  - Taxes-Federal (990), 1985-1991 (Box 17)
  - Dr. Leon Tec (Box 17)
  - Temenos Institute (Dr. Joseph Wagenseller) (Box 17)
  - Dr. John W. Thibaut (Box 17)
  - Henry C. Thomas (Box 17)
  - Dr. Charles B. Thompson (Box 17)
  - Dr. Charles B. Thompson-manuscript (Box 17)
  - Mrs. Phyllis Thomsen (Box 17)
  - Dr. Giske Tomita (Box 17)
  - Dr. William R. Torbert (Box 17)
  - Towards Integral Consciousness (TIC) (Box 17)
  - Towards Integral Consciousness requests (Box 17)
  - TIC-Reviews & References (Box 17)
  - Toward Social Sanity & Human Survival (TSS&HS)--Index (Box 17)
  - TSS & HS--Sales Material (Box 17)
  - TSS & HS--Library Mailing, 1987 (Box 17)
  - TSS & HS--Requests from University Libraries (Box 17)
  - TSS & HS-Acknowledgments (Box 17)
  - TSS & HS-Reviews (Box 18)
  - TSS & HS-Miscellaneous (Box 18)
  - TSS & HS-Titles (Box 18)
  - TSS & HS-List of Book Reviewers (Box 18)
  - Transformation of Consciousness-Montreal Â· Conference, 1973 (Box 18)
  - Translators (Box 18)
  - Mrs. Helen Traub (Box 18)
  - Dr. Colin Turnbull (Box 18)
  - T-Tz (Box 18)
  - UN University for Peace (Box 18)
  - Dr. Montague Ullman, 1973-1991 (Box 18)
  - Judge & Mrs. Joseph N. Ulman (Box 18)
  - H. A. Unvala (Box 18)
  - U- Uz (Box 18)
  - Dr. & Mrs. René Vaillant (Box 18)
  - Viking Press (Box 18)
  - Dr. S. L. Vinekar (Box 18)
  - Dr. Ludwig von Bertalanffy (Box 18)
  - V - Vz (Box 19)
  - Kevin Wallace (Box 19)
  - Alan W. Watts (Box 19)
  - Florence Weatherly-Bishop with manuscript (Box 19)
  - Mrs. Edward W. Weingartner (Box 19)
  - Wenner-Gren Foundation (Box 19)
  - Dr. Frederick Wertham (Box 19)
  - Westport Library (Box 19)
  - John White (Box 19)
  - Dr. Cornelius Wholey (Box 19)
  - Lancelot Law Whyte (Box 19)
  - Jack Wikse, 1977-1992 (Box 19)
  - J. Talbot Winchell (Box 19)
  - William Withers (Box 19)
  - Mrs. Miriam Bredow Wolf (Box 19)
  - Dr. Philip Woollcott (Box 19)
  - Samuel Woolf (Box 19)
  - Peter T. Wotton (Box 19)
  - W-Wz (Box 19)
  - Yale University, 1954-1986 (Box 20)
  - David Yandell, 1973-1984 (Box 20)
  - XYZ (Box 20)
  - Diary, 1932-1991 (Box 20)
  - Outgoing Mail, 1951-1989 (Box 20)
  - Incoming Mail, 1951-1989 (Box 21)
  - Financial records
    - Florence A. Guggenheimer Trust (FAG) (Box 21)
    - FAG-Trust Fund Correspondence, 1953-1988 (Box 21)
    - FAG-Trust Fund Income Tax, 1953-1979 (Box 21)
    - Norfolk National Bank of Commerce (Box 21)
    - Trigant Burrow Trust, 1973-1987 (Box 21)
    - Trigant Burrow Trust, 1950-1972 (Box 21)
    - Tax Reports Reports & Correspondence-Federal, 1978-1984 (Box 21)
    - Tax Reports Reports & Correspondence-Federal, 1972-1977 (Box 21)
    - Federal Tax Withheld (Box 21)
    - Tax Reports & Correspondence-CT State (Box 21)
    - Tax Reports & Correspondence-MD State (Box 21)
    - Real Estate Tax (Box 21)
    - General Ledgers, 1944-1967 (Box 22)
    - General Ledgers, 1972-1989 (Box 22)
    - Annual Financial Reports, 1950-1989 (Box 22)
    - Cash Receipts, 1981-1991 (Box 23)
    - Lifwynn Special CR's & CD's (over-sized), 1955-1972 (Box 23–24)
  - Restricted Files (Box 25)
    Materials are restricted for 75 years from date of creation (1950-1988), and will be available for research between 2026 and 2064.